

carafalcon@gmail.com www.carafalcon.com github.com/carafalcon

FREELANCE DESIGNER / WEB DEVELOPER

BIO

I'm a 25 year old Freelance Designer/Web Developer and Mobile Ad Analyst based in Toronto.

I took an interest in design and development at the age of 12, when I began tinkering with creative software such as Adobe Photoshop, and coding languages such as HTML & CSS. In my free time, I can be found browsing the webdesign subreddit, weightlifting, daydreaming about Hawaii, or eating sushi.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, MARKETING

University of Toronto 2010 - 2014

EXPERIENCE

MANAGER, AD OPERATIONS

Upsight | February 2018 - Present

- Be the front line contact for 15+ ad partner relationships and negotiate deal terms to drive ad revenue for publishers mobile apps
- · Lead Ad Operations team of 2 other members and oversee all day-to-day operations
- · Manage onboarding process of new ad network partnerships from first POC to live traffic launch

CREATIVE MANAGER & LEAD DEVELOPER (VOLUNTEER)

Sudo Labs | May 2016 - Present

- Develop Sudo website with HTML, SCSS, Gulp, and Bootstrap CSS Framework
- Design marketing collateral (Logo, Facebook cover photos, Sponsorship Package, Business Cards)
 with Adobe Photoshop

SENIOR MOBILE AD ANALYST

Upsight | January 2016 - February 2018

- Monitor and review publisher performance, create and analyze customized reports by querying data with SQL, and identify actionable opportunities to maximize revenue growth
- Train incoming Ad Operation hires on internal systems, processes and best practices, as well as document standard operating procedures
- Collaborate with QA, SDK, and Support teams to troubleshoot issues

FREELANCE DESIGNER/WEB DEVELOPER

June 2013 - Present

- Design and deliver mockups for development team to follow and run iterations to ensure client visions are aligned
- Identify design problems and devise elegant solutions
- Code website layout/user interfaces using standard HTML/CSS practices

Skillset Overview

- · Languages: HTML, CSS, Basic JavaScript
- · Design Tools: Sketch, Photoshop
- VCS: GitHub
- · Automation: Gulp

MOBILE AD COORDINATOR

Fuse Powered (Acquired by Upsight, Jan. 2016) | May 2014 - January 2016

- Acquired, coordinated, and delivered high performing CPI advertising campaigns (direct deals and cross-promotions)
- Negotiated pricing and traffic volumes based off KPIs
- Onboarded new apps for ad mediation across multiple ad networks

VICE PRESIDENT OF MARKETING (VOLUNTEER)

Investment Society, Finance Student Group October 2013 - May 2014

- · Designed marketing collateral (posters, pamphlets, business cards) with Adobe Photoshop
- Managed marketing, communications, and IT departments by delegating tasks and ensuring deadlines are met

PROJECT OFFICER (AUDIT DIVISION)

Canada Revenue Agency | January 2013 - April 2014

- · Reviewed and updated confidential account information upon requirements
- Contacted clients via telephone or written correspondence letters
- Organized and entered data using Microsoft Office Suites

WEBMASTER

University of Toronto November 2012 - April 2014

- · Integrated updates and new postings into existing website using Adobe Dreamweaver
- · Posted new videos and photos to support content via website and Facebook
- · Designed marketing collateral (event posters) with Adobe Photoshop for the UofT athletics department

References available upon request